# André Henriques

Mobile: \_+44 (0) 7823 391342 Email: andr3h3nriqu3s@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrehenriques-0240b1205/ andr3h3nriqu3s.com

# **PROFILE**

Flexible, logical and resourceful software developer with experience in web development and Linux system administrator. My curiosity knows no bound, and I am always trying to learn more about a new technologies and subjects. Love to code and love to be challenged with interesting projects. Adaptive in my work, so it can increase performance and be easily reused by me or other developers.

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Portuguese, English
- Proficient in Javascript, Java, HTML/CSS, React, Svelte, Linux
- Some knowledge in Rust, Go, SQL, zig, C++, Dart, Flutter, Python
- Critical Thinking
- Fast Learner

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Planum Solucoes Lda, Software Developer**

'June 2020 - Present

- Developed a variety of websites using React and Svelte
- Implemented DevOps with GitLab CI/CD tools
- Enhanced Bug reporting with GitLab Issues
- Linux Server Administration
- Some of the projects
  - Dr Play: Provides medical support services and a telemedicine platform
    - Developed multi-profile user portal <u>front.drplay.com.br</u>
    - Developed product website drplay.com.br
    - Implemented Java library to dynamic link classes to databases
    - Designing a WebRTC video call system.
    - Some implemented features: medical record, user, product and supplier management; dashboards; CMS.
  - o Numo: Benefits platform for employees of affiliated companies
    - Developed multi-profile user portal <u>front.usenumo.com.br</u>
    - Developed product website usenumo.com.br
    - Integration with Google APIs for region delimiting
    - Some implemented features: campaign, message, user, product and supplier management; dashboards; CMS.
  - Icargo: Platform that links truck drivers and companies
    - Developed multi-profile user portal
    - Developed product website <u>icargo.usenumo.com.br</u>
    - Use Google APIs for geo-locating
    - Some implemented features: fleet, cargo, user, product and supplier management; dashboards; CMS.

#### **University of Surrey, Lab Pal**

Sept 2021 - Present

• I help students with their lab work by explaining the subject or the exercise they are having problems with.

# **EDUCATION**

University of Surrey, Bcs (Hons) Computer Science (Achieved 1 on the 1st year) Sept 2020 - June 2024 Externato Joao Alberto Faria (Portuguese High school achieved 17/20) Sept 2008 - June 2020

# **INTERESTS & HOBBIES**

- I enjoy playing video games and watching enjoy.
  I love learning about a variety of themes from coding to physics.
- Have some projects that I use to explore different languages and or technologies (more information can be found on my website)